kissandmakeup.tv 2013-12-23

# Kiss And Makeup's Privacy Policy on Kiss And Makeup

This privacy policy sets out how the Aigua Megazine Group uses and protects any information that you give Aigua Media when you use this website.

Aigua Media is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Aigua Media may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2 November 2011.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may send promotional emails about news, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Cookies used on Kiss And Makeup

**Type of Cookie**

| 

**What do they do?**

| 

**Do these cookies collect my personal data / identify me?**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Necessary

| 

These cookies are essential to make Kiss And Makeup websites work correctly, they enable you to move around our websites and use our features. Examples include remembering previous actions (e.g. entered text) when navigating back to a page in the same session.

| 

These cookies don't identify you as an individual.

If you do not accept these cookies, it may affect the performance of the website, or parts of it.  
  
Performance

| 

These cookies help us understand how visitors interact with our websites by providing information about the areas visited, the time spent on the website, and any issues encountered, such as error messages. This helps us improve the performance of our websites.

| 

These cookies don't identify you as an individual. All data is collected and aggregated anonymously.  
  
Functionality

| 

These cookies allow our websites to remember the choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) to provide a more personalised online experience. They can also enable visitors to watch videos, play games and engage with social tools, such as blogs, chatrooms and forums.

| 

The information these cookies collect may include personally identifiable information that you have disclosed, such as your username or profile picture. We shall always be transparent with you about what information we collect, what we do with it and with whom we share it.

If you do not accept these cookies, it may affect the performance and functionality of the website and may restrict access to content on the website.  
  
Targeting / advertising

| 

These cookies are used to deliver content that is more relevant to you and your interests. They may be used to deliver targeted advertising or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They also help us measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns on Kiss And Makeup and non-Kiss And Makeup websites.

We may use these cookies to remember websites you have visited and we may share this information with other parties, including advertisers and our agencies.

| 

Most types of these cookies track consumers via their [IP address](http://www.techterms.com/definition/ipaddress) so may collect some personal identifiable information.  
  
### Measuring website usage (Google Analytics)

We use Google Analytics to collect information about how people use this site. We do this to make sure it’s meeting its users’ needs and to understand how we could do it better.

Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. We do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. We do not allow Google to use or share our analytics data.

The following cookies are set by Google Analytics:

Name | Purpose | Expires  
---|---|---  
_utma | This randomly generated number is used to determine unique visitors to our site | 2 years  
_utmb | This randomly generated number works with _utmc to calculate the average length of time users spend on our site | 30 minutes  
_utmc | This randomly generated number works with _utmb to calculate when you close your browser | when you close your browser  
_utmz | This is a randomly generated number and information about how the site was reached (e.g. direct or via a link, organic search or paid search) | 6 months  
GDS_successEvents  
GDS_analyticsTokens | These cookies help us identify how people use GOV.UK so we can make the site better | 4 months  
  
## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us [here](mailto:info@aiguamedia.com?subject=Contact%20Request%20From%20Kiss%20And%20Makeup "Contact Aiguamedia").

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [Aigua Media](http://www.aiguamedia.com/ "Aiguamedia the megazine"), The Met Building, 22 Percy Street, London, W1T 2BU.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
